[
    {"question": "いくさ", "answer": "戦"},
    {"question": "かみなり", "answer": "雷"},
    {"question": "にちぼつ", "answer": "日没"},
    {"question": "あいしゅう", "answer": "哀愁"},
    {"question": "すもう", "answer": "相撲"},
    {"question": "かんよう", "answer": "寛容"},
    {"question": "せきつい", "answer": "脊椎"},
    {"question": "つるみ", "answer": "鶴見"},
    {"question": "けいじ", "answer": "慶事"},
    {"question": "がっしょう", "answer": "合掌"},
    {"question": "どうたい", "answer": "胴体"},
    {"question": "えがお", "answer": "笑顔"},
    {"question": "らくのう", "answer": "酪農"},
    {"question": "きゅうどう", "answer": "弓道"},
    {"question": "ぬう", "answer": "縫う"},
    {"question": "ちょうでん", "answer": "弔電"},
    {"question": "ちょうせん", "answer": "挑戦"},
    {"question": "かしこい", "answer": "賢い"},
    {"question": "つゆ", "answer": "梅雨"},
    {"question": "かま", "answer": "鎌"},
    {"question": "おくれる", "answer": "後れる"},
    {"question": "いっきとうせん", "answer": "一騎当千"},
    {"question": "とむらう", "answer": "弔う"},
    {"question": "がいかん", "answer": "概観"},
    {"question": "もっかん", "answer": "木棺"},
    {"question": "さみだれ", "answer": "五月雨"},
    {"question": "ほ", "answer": "穂"},
    {"question": "でし", "answer": "弟子"},
    {"question": "うすげしょう", "answer": "薄化粧"},
    {"question": "ほる", "answer": "彫る"},
    {"question": "かいこん", "answer": "悔恨"},
    {"question": "きょうしゅう", "answer": "郷愁"},
    {"question": "さつき", "answer": "五月"},
    {"question": "かる", "answer": "刈る"},
    {"question": "さずかる", "answer": "授かる"},
    {"question": "びれい", "answer": "美麗"},
    {"question": "せんと", "answer": "遷都"},
    {"question": "かっとう", "answer": "葛藤"},
    {"question": "けんそん", "answer": "謙遜"},
    {"question": "しぐれ", "answer": "時雨"},
    {"question": "かまめし", "answer": "釜飯"},
    {"question": "ほど", "answer": "程"},
    {"question": "くやむ", "answer": "悔やむ"},
    {"question": "とくめい", "answer": "匿名"},
    {"question": "かくしん", "answer": "核心"},
    {"question": "そうほう", "answer": "双方"},
    {"question": "かぜ", "answer": "風邪"},
    {"question": "あし", "answer": "脚"},
    {"question": "かみわざ", "answer": "神業"},
    {"question": "そで", "answer": "袖"},
    {"question": "めんせき", "answer": "免責"},
    {"question": "せいぎょ", "answer": "制御"},
    {"question": "はくちゅう", "answer": "伯仲"},
    {"question": "ひより", "answer": "日和"},
    {"question": "けんさく", "answer": "検索"},
    {"question": "うる", "answer": "得る"},
    {"question": "ふくろ", "answer": "袋"},
    {"question": "しっそう", "answer": "失踪"},
    {"question": "おんれい", "answer": "御礼"},
    {"question": "きっぽう", "answer": "吉報"},
    {"question": "ここち", "answer": "心地"},
    {"question": "かんだい", "answer": "寛大"},
    {"question": "さくさん", "answer": "酢酸"},
    {"question": "しきい", "answer": "敷居"},
    {"question": "さしょう", "answer": "詐称"},
    {"question": "いどむ", "answer": "挑む"},
    {"question": "ぶんだん", "answer": "文壇"},
    {"question": "みやげ", "answer": "土産"},
    {"question": "かまくら", "answer": "鎌倉"},
    {"question": "にもの", "answer": "煮物"},
    {"question": "さいほう", "answer": "裁縫"},
    {"question": "すなはま", "answer": "砂浜"},
    {"question": "うらむ", "answer": "恨む"},
    {"question": "ろうばしん", "answer": "老婆心"},
    {"question": "けんきょ", "answer": "謙虚"},
    {"question": "ほさき", "answer": "穂先"},
    {"question": "いしうす", "answer": "石臼"},
    {"question": "かれい", "answer": "華麗"},
    {"question": "しゅんそく", "answer": "俊足"},
    {"question": "ふじ", "answer": "藤"},
    {"question": "こうはい", "answer": "後輩"},
    {"question": "ふたご", "answer": "双子"},
    {"question": "す", "answer": "酢"},
    {"question": "つまる", "answer": "詰まる"},
    {"question": "こうかい", "answer": "後悔"},
    {"question": "びこう", "answer": "鼻孔"},
    {"question": "おば", "answer": "叔母"},
    {"question": "さむらい", "answer": "侍"},
    {"question": "きちじつ", "answer": "吉日"},
    {"question": "にこむ", "answer": "煮込む"},
    {"question": "かんぷ", "answer": "完膚"},
    {"question": "くやしい", "answer": "悔しい"},
    {"question": "あいじょう", "answer": "愛嬢"},
    {"question": "かいきょう", "answer": "海峡"},
    {"question": "いっぺん", "answer": "一遍"},
    {"question": "じい", "answer": "侍医"},
    {"question": "きゅうし", "answer": "臼歯"},
    {"question": "はんも", "answer": "繁茂"},
    {"question": "らいめい", "answer": "雷鳴"},
    {"question": "へんせん", "answer": "変遷"},
    {"question": "どうい", "answer": "胴衣"},
    {"question": "がな", "answer": "仮名"},
    {"question": "ふへんてき", "answer": "普遍的"},
    {"question": "つめる", "answer": "詰める"},
    {"question": "ようせい", "answer": "妖精"},
    {"question": "おうとつ", "answer": "凹凸"},
    {"question": "めんきょ", "answer": "免許"},
    {"question": "けんめい", "answer": "賢明"},
    {"question": "しゃみせん", "answer": "三味線"},
    {"question": "くるまいす", "answer": "車椅子"},
    {"question": "じゅうてん", "answer": "充填"},
    {"question": "こがら", "answer": "小柄"},
    {"question": "けいちょう", "answer": "慶弔"},
    {"question": "さしゅ", "answer": "詐取"},
    {"question": "しんちょく", "answer": "進捗"},
    {"question": "たび", "answer": "足袋"},
    {"question": "さんきゃく", "answer": "三脚"},
    {"question": "けつまく", "answer": "結膜"},
    {"question": "ひざ", "answer": "膝"},
    {"question": "ちょうこく", "answer": "彫刻"},
    {"question": "かいひん", "answer": "海浜"},
    {"question": "めいふく", "answer": "冥福"},
    {"question": "ぞうり", "answer": "草履"},
    {"question": "たんさく", "answer": "探索"},
    {"question": "ひふ", "answer": "皮膚"},
    {"question": "てさげ", "answer": "手提げ"},
    {"question": "にんしん", "answer": "妊娠"},
    {"question": "れいじょう", "answer": "令嬢"},
    {"question": "しゅっかん", "answer": "出棺"},
    {"question": "たち", "answer": "太刀"},
    {"question": "いかく", "answer": "威嚇"},
    {"question": "しょほうせん", "answer": "処方箋"},
    {"question": "ひとみ", "answer": "瞳"},
    {"question": "とうじょう", "answer": "搭乗"},
    {"question": "ごはん", "answer": "御飯"},
    {"question": "ろうおう", "answer": "老翁"},
    {"question": "しない", "answer": "竹刀"},
    {"question": "しゅうちしん", "answer": "羞恥心"},
    {"question": "かいぼう", "answer": "解剖"},
    {"question": "むすめ", "answer": "娘"}
]
